[Destiny and Saving] [EP20]
She has been waiting for you for a long time.
How's the situation outside?
She has calmed down the inner court.
But
Chu Nanfeng seems to know
that you are injured.
What are you doing?
Trying to rape me?
Who's trying to rape whom?
And you're injured.
My Lady,
sorry,
I forgot this.
This is the porridge made for you.
I'll put it here.
Today is not a good day.
Let me feed you some porridge.
Okay,
I'll listen to you.
You've injured your muscles and bones,
you need to boost your energy and blood.
I had the kitchen
add some astragalus and
codonopsis to the porridge.
It's good for you.
Is the porridge cold?
I'll get you some hot porridge,
or maybe you want some hot water?
I'll get you a cup of water.
Don't move.
Miss Ye Jinrou has already...
She's awake.
I asked her to reflect in the yard.
And
the hospital also said
that Abao has shown signs of waking up.
When you're well,
we can go see him.
Anything else?
Ling Shenxing and Su Muwan
are really lucky
to survive like this.
Ye Jinrou is such a good-for-nothing.
Second Concubine,
the young master is awake.
He's been crying.
Treat him.
Find the best doctor in the city.
You must cure the young master's
asthma.
Is it your stepfather who beat you again?
It's him.
He said my brother needed money to get married,
so he asked me for money.
I listened to you.
I didn't give him a penny.
Then my stepfather
beat me to death.
Go down.
Go down and have a rest.
Yes.
You're here.
You've heard about it, haven't you?
Tell me.
What are you going to do in the future?
You gave me the note
to
work together to
get rid of Su Muwan.
You can deal with
the rest as you wish.
Are you in love with this girl?
Chu Nanfeng,
I found out
that
you put the jade pendant
on the body
of Grand Marshal Ling
to frame the Sus.
And the radio station
has been quiet.
The head of the Su family
hasn't shown up as promised.
Is there
something wrong in the city?
Marshal,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
The news that those people didn't get intercepted
have all been blocked by us.
Besides,
the news of the disappearance of Commander Ling
has spread all over the city.
Ling Shenxing and the others
may soon find their way here.
The water in this city
needs to be muddier.
Ye Jinrou of the Ye family
is a menace.
She's a liability.
You just need to listen to me.
Don't hurt Su Muwan.
Leave the rest
to me.
After it's done, the Lings will be yours.
The position of the marshal will be mine.
I'll deal with
this fake marshal for you.
Deal.
I knew I could count on you.
Chu Nanfeng,
you are
so ruthless.
One more thing.
My maid's
stepfather,
I want him to have an accident.
Okay.
Immediately.
I have done what you asked.
The beggar infected with the plague
has been sent
to the busiest street.
Good.
Let the situation in Yang City
become more and more chaotic.
Thank you.
Don't
do anything stupid like this again.
You didn't study toxicology.
You'd better
stay away from Ghost Vine.
What's Ghost Vine?
I've never heard of it.
You didn't touch my medicine?
I asked Cuijuan to change the prescription.
It's all tonic.
I just asked them to increase the dosage.
It makes people weak
after taking,
but not poisonous.
Cuijuan,
I did follow
this prescription.
The doctor checked it
and said it would only make the body weak.
Please spare me, Young Madam.
Besides you,
who else has touched my medicine?
And,
Second Concubine's
Chuntao.
She often watches the furnace for me.
You may go.
Yes.
I'll give you two choices.
First,
marry into the Ling Family
as a cousin.
After the storm,
we'll fake your death
The Young Marshal and I will give you a new identity
and let you leave Yang City.
This is a blank marriage certificate.
Fill it out yourself.
Second,
leave the Ye family
and start your own business.
This is the shop in the busiest place of Yang City.
It's yours now.
What about the profit?
We'll split it 80/20.
You take 80%,
and we take 20%.
Of course,
I won't take this 20% for nothing.
You can use the name of Ling family
at any time.
No one will bully you.
Choose.
Thank you.